Contact

irishfan269@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/bobbie-murphy-59514024 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Registered Nurses Inpatient BLS

Bobbie Murphy

VP of Patient Care & CNO

Bristol, Tennessee

Summary

Nursing has been a profession that has empowered me to personally connect with patients, peers, and families. This profession offers the opportunity to truly impact the lives of others. I am honored and humbled by my professional experience each day. Nursing is not only my profession, it is a part of who I am.

Experience

Ballad Health
Chief Nursing Officer
October 2017 - Present (2 years 10 months)
Southwest Virginia

Wellmont Health System
Director ED, Critical Care, Trauma, Respiratory
November 2016 - Present (3 years 9 months)
Kingsport, Tennessee

Covenant Health
Director of Patient Care Services
September 2014 - November 2016 (2 years 3 months)
Morristown TN

Bronson Healthcare

4 years

Director Behavioral Health September 2012 - September 2014 (2 years 1 month)

Nurse Manager October 2010 - September 2012 (2 years) Behavioral Health Services

Bronson Battle Creek Staff RN February 2010 - October 2010 (9 months)

Critical Care

Beacon Specialized Living Services RN 2007 - 2010 (3 years)

Bronson Methodist Hospital Staff RN April 2002 - May 2007 (5 years 2 months) Trauma Care Unit

Education

Western Governors University

Master of Science (MS), Nursing Administration · (2015 - 2016)

Ferris State University

Master of Science (MS), Nursing · (2010 - 2015)

Ferris State University
Bachelor of Science (BS), Nursing · (2007 - 2010)

Western Governors University

Masters in Business Administration (2016)